"Key_FlarisWar"
{	
	Say("Oh. Mr.Stin told you that.. I see. I think he can use his brain. Are you wondering what I am talking about?");
	Say("Listen. This equipment,Lodelight,was made by the prince of Flaris,Parrt,and the best magician of Flaris,Mr.Bein.");
	Say("The religious doctrine of Resis is that everything in this world has its own soul.  How cannot you know such a thing?");
	Say("The spirit of human who has lost his<her> life does not disappear suddenly and exists in this world for a while.  The soul and body could be united again by the Lodelight in that while.");
	Say("But not this is not an omnipotent equipment. Only people who had got killed can be resurrected here.");
	Say("This equipment will be very helpful,if there is a war.  Prince Parrt would think of that.");
	Say("Therefore,the person of the blood on your knife can be resurrected with the blood.");
	Say("Do you understand? This knife will be the obvious evidence");
	Say("Bring this knife to Juria.");
	SetQuestState(QUEST_SCENARIO2, 4);
}
